socialreport.com 2019-10-17

# Privacy Policy | Social Report

### Social Report Privacy Policy

We at Social Report (SocialReport.com) are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy applies to both our Website (www.socialreport.com) and our Subscription Service (the Subscription Service), including our associated mobile applications (Mobile Apps) owned and controlled by Social Report. This Privacy Policy governs our data collection, processing and usage practices. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information. If you do not agree with the data practices described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Website or the Subscription Service. 

We periodically update this Privacy Policy. We will post any privacy policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice by sending you an email notification, or if you subscribe to the Subscription Service, through the Notification app in your Social Report portal. 

While we will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy, we encourage you to review this Privacy Policy periodically. We will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our treatment of the information you provide us, please write to us by email at privacy@socialreport.com or by mail to SocialReport.com, 15400 SE 30th Place, Suite 202, Bellevue, WA 98007 USA, Attn: Privacy. 

### Use of the Subscription Service by Social Report and our Customers

#### The Social Report Subscription Service

Our online Subscription Service allows any company that uses it (our customers and Social Report itself) to create and share marketing, sales and customer service content. The Subscription Service can also be used to help organize sales data about a company’s sales pipeline (e.g., leads, customers, deals, etc.). The information added to the Subscription Service, either by site visitors providing their contact information or when a Subscription Service user adds the information, is stored and managed on our service providers' servers. This information is then used to contact visitors about their interest in the company's goods or services and interact with the company. Social Report provides the Subscription Service to our customers for their own marketing, lead generation, and customer service needs, and we use it to meet Social Report’s related needs.

#### Use by Social Report

We use our own Subscription Service to build webpages that people can visit to learn more about Social Report. Information that we collect and manage using the Subscription Service for our own marketing belongs to us and is used, disclosed and protected according to this Privacy Policy.

#### Use by Our Customers

Our customers use the Subscription Service to build webpages that people can visit to learn more about their business. Social Report does not control the content of these webpages or the types of information that our customers may choose to collect or manage using the Subscription Service. That information belongs to them and is used, disclosed and protected by them according to their privacy policies and is not subject to this Privacy Policy. Social Report processes our customers' information as they direct and in accordance with our agreements with our customers, and we store it on our service providers' servers, but we do not have control over its collection or management. Our agreements with our customers prohibit us from using that information, except as necessary to provide and improve the Subscription Service, as permitted by this Privacy Policy, and as required by law. We have no direct relationship with individuals who provide Personal Information to our customers. Social Report acknowledges that you have the right to access your Personal Information. Our customers control and are responsible for correcting, deleting or updating information they have collected from you using the Subscription Service. If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe. We may work with our customers to help them provide notice to their visitors about their data collection, processing and usage. Our agreements with our customers prohibit them from using the Subscription Service to collect, manage, or process Sensitive Information. We are not responsible for our customers' use of information they collect on the Subscription Service.

Social Report collects information under the direction of its customers, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose Personal Information it processes. If you are a customer of one of our customers and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our customer that use our Subscription Service, please contact the customer that you interact with directly. We may transfer Personal Information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our customers.

#### "Sensitive Information"

This refers to credit or debit card numbers, personal financial account information, Social Security numbers, passport numbers, driver's license numbers or similar personal identifiers, racial or ethnic origin, physical or mental health condition or information, or other employment, financial or health information.

### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
  * To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * To process transactions

###  How We Use Information We Collect 

#### Compliance with Our Privacy Policy

We use the information we collect only in compliance with this Privacy Policy. Customers who subscribe to our Subscription Services are obligated through our agreements with them to comply with this Privacy Policy.

#### We Never Sell Personal Information

We will never sell your Personal Information to any third party.

#### Use of Personal Information

In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this Privacy Policy, we may use your Personal Information to:

  * improve your browsing experience by personalizing the Websites and to improve the Subscription Service;
  * send information or Social Report content to you which we think may be of interest to you by post, email, or other means and send you marketing communications relating to our business;
  * provide other companies with statistical information about our users -- but this information will not be used to identify any individual user;
  * send information to you regarding changes to our Customer Terms of Service, Privacy Policy (including the Cookie Policy), or other legal agreements 
  * meet legal requirements.

We may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, we do not transfer your Personal Information to the third party.

We use the information collected through our Subscription Service by our customers for the following purposes:

  * to provide the Subscription Service (which may include the detection, prevention and resolution of security and technical issues);
  * to respond to customer support requests; and
  * otherwise to fulfill the obligations under the Social Report Customer Terms of Service.
  * Legal basis for processing Personal Information (EEA visitors only)

If you are a visitor/customer located in the European Economic Area ("EEA"), Social Report Ireland Limited is the data controller of your personal information. Social Report's Data Protection Officer can be contacted at privacy@socialreport.com.

Our legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described above will depend on the personal information concerned and the specific context in which we collect it. However, we will normally collect personal information from you only where we have your consent to do so, where we need the personal information to perform a contract with you, or where the processing is in our legitimate interests and not overridden by your data protection interests or fundamental rights and freedoms. In some cases, we may also have a legal obligation to collect personal information from you.

If we ask you to provide personal information to comply with a legal requirement or to perform a contract with you, we will make this clear at the relevant time and advise you whether the provision of your personal information is mandatory or not (as well as of the possible consequences if you do not provide your personal information). Similarly, if we collect and use your personal information in reliance on our legitimate interests (or those of any third party), we will make clear to you at the relevant time what those legitimate interests are.

#### Use of Navigational Information

We use Navigational Information to operate and improve the Websites and the Subscription Service. We may also use Navigational Information alone or in combination with Personal Information to provide you with personalized information about Social Report.

#### Customer Testimonials and Comments

We post customer testimonials and comments on our Websites, which may contain Personal Information. We obtain each customer's consent via email prior to posting the customer's name and testimonial.

#### Use of Credit Card Information

If you give us credit card information, we use it solely to check your financial qualifications and collect payment from you. We use a third-party service provider to manage credit card processing. This service provider is not permitted to store, retain, or use information you provide except for the sole purpose of credit card processing on our behalf.

#### Security of your Personal Information

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. We secure the Personal Information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. All Personal Information is protected using appropriate physical, technical and organizational measures.

#### Social Media Features

Our Websites include Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share This button or interactive mini-programs that run on our sites. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our sites, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these features. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy and other policies of the companies providing them.

#### External Websites

Our Websites provide links to other websites. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the content or practices of these other websites. Our provision of such links does not constitute our endorsement of these other websites, their content, their owners, or their practices. This Privacy Policy does not apply to these other websites, which are subject to any privacy and other policies they may have.

#### Public Forums

We offer publicly accessible message boards, blogs, and community forums. Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose any information through our public message boards, blogs, or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. We will correct or delete any information you have posted on the Websites if you so request, as described in "Opting Out and Unsubscribing" below.

#### Retention of Personal Information

How long we keep information we collect about you depends on the type of information. as described in further detail below. After such time, we will either delete or anonymize your information or, if this is not possible, then we will securely store your information and isolate it from any further use until deletion is possible.

We retain Personal Information that you provide to us where we have an ongoing legitimate business need to do so (for example, as long as is required in order to contact you about the Subscription Service or our other services, or as needed to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements).

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your Personal Information, we securely delete the information or anonymise it or, if this is not possible, then we will securely store your Personal Information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible. We will delete this information from the servers at an earlier date if you so request, as described in "To Unsubscribe from Our Communcations" below.

If you provide information to our customers as part of their use of the Subscription Service, our customers decide how long to retain the personal information they collect from you. If a customer terminates its use of the Subscription Service, then we will provide customer with access to all information stored for the customer by the Subscription Service, including any Personal Information provided by you, for export by the customer according to our agreement with our customer. After termination, we may, unless legally prohibited, delete all customer information, including your Personal Information, from the Subscription Service.

If you have elected to receive marketing communications from us, we retain information about your marketing preferences for a reasonable period of time from the date you last expressed interest in our content, products, or services, such as when you last opened an email from us or ceased using your Social Report account. We retain information derived from cookies and other tracking technologies for a reasonable period of time from the date such information was created.

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit card number, billing address) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

### Privacy Shield Notice

Social Report participates in and has certified its compliance with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss–U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. The following affiliated entities adhere to the Privacy Shield principles: Social Report Ireland Limited, Social Report Germany GmbH, Social Report Australia Pty Ltd, Social Report Asia Pte. Ltd., and Social Report Japan KK. Social Report is committed to subjecting all personal data received from European Union (EU) member countries and Switzerland, in reliance on the Privacy Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles. To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List at https://www.privacyshield.gov.

Social Report is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives under the Privacy Shield Framework and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as an agent on its behalf. Social Report complies with the Privacy Shield Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU and Switzerland, including the onward transfer liability provisions.

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Social Report is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission. In certain situations, Social Report may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

You may direct any inquiries or complaints related to our Privacy Shield compliance to privacy@socialeport.com. If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, you may contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.

Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website, you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted.

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

### Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits.

### Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

### Children Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

### Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

### Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website 

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy. 

###  How to Access & Control Your Personal Data 

#### Reviewing, Correcting and Removing Your Personal Information

You have the following data protection rights:

  * You can request access, correction, updates or deletion of your personal information.
  * You can object to processing of your personal information, ask us to restrict processing of your personal information or request portability of your personal information.
  * If we have collected and process your personal information with your consent, then you can withdraw your consent at any time. Withdrawing your consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we conducted prior to your withdrawal, nor will it affect processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.
  * You have the right to complain to a data protection authority about our collection and use of your personal information. Contact details for data protection authorities in the EEA, Switzerland and certain non-European countries (including the US and Canada) are available here.)
  * To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at privacy@socialreport.com or by mail to SocialReport.com, 15400 SE 30th Place, Suite 202, Bellevue, WA 98007, USA, Attention: Privacy. We will respond to your request to change, correct, or delete your information within a reasonable timeframe and notify you of the action we have taken.

#### To Unsubscribe From Our Communications

You may unsubscribe from our marketing communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of our e-mails, updating your communication preferences, or by sending us email us at privacy@Social Report.com or postal mail to SocialReport.com, 15400 SE 30th Place, Suite 202, Bellevue, WA 98007, USA, Attention: Privacy. Customers cannot opt out of receiving transactional emails related to their account with us or the Subscription Service.

#### To Unsubscribe from Our Customers' Communications

Our customers are solely responsible for their own marketing emails and other communications; we cannot unsubscribe you from their communications. You can unsubscribe from our customers' marketing communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of their emails, or by contacting them directly.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

  * SocialReport.com  
15400 SE 30th Place, Suite 202  
Bellevue, WA 98007
  * https://www.socialreport.com
  * privacy@socialreport.com
